Register of the Frederick L. Anderson papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Motion Picture Film, undated
  - "Mr. Churchill's Cuba Trip" (color), 8 minutes, circa 1945 (Reel 25)
    16mm reversal print, silent, unedited. Features footage of Clementine Churchill, Winston Churchill, Miami, Florida, Sarah Churchill, the “Mary Winn II” bomber, shots of pilots, aerial shots of sea and land, and scenes of Churchill’s motorcade in Cuba.